## Bruno Criado

Pederneiras, SP, Brazil brunocriado@gmail.com Phone: 55 14 98136 8331

#### Summary

Graduate in Computer area having over 12 years of experience in IT infrastructure and software development. Looking now for new challenges and opportunities that allow him to learn new technologies and work with new people. Great interest in R&D in Sofware Development.

#### Education

Universidade Católica de Brasilia, Graduate in Information Security

# Industry Experience

## Infrastructure Developer

Nov 2015 - Present

Flugel.it - https://www.flugel.it

Main Technologies: Cloud Computing, Python, Configuration Management Tools, Orchestration/Provisioning Tools, Containers;

## Responsabilities:

- Automating and implementing solutions using script languages and DevOps Tools
- Creating and developing system to aggregate value to client products
- Using Continuos Deployment to build Infrastructure

# Software Engineer

Set 2012 - Aug 2015

MStech - http://www.mstech.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux, Python, C/C++, Virtualization.

# Responsabilities:

- Maintain a multi-plata form solution for remote boot and hard disk protection on storage virtualization
- Maintain a Linux distribution for hard drive imaging purpose
- Developing products for managing classrooms

# Senior IT Infrastructure Analyst

May 2011 - Jul 2012

 $Fidelity\ Information\ Service$  - https://www.fisglobal.com

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Cisco devices (Firewall, Router, Switches), Network Protocols/Services, Virtualization.

#### Responsabilities:

- Maintain network computer safe and healthy.
- Monitoring network services/devices.
- Automated Security Tests

# IT Infrastructure Analyst

Jan 2010 - Apr 2011

Eprom - http://www.eprom.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Router, Switches, Network Protocols/Services, Virtualization.

#### Responsabilities:

- Maintain network computer safe and healthy.
- Monitoring network services/devices.
- Technical Support

## IT Infrastructure Analyst

Inforeason - http://www.inforeason.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Router, Switches, Network Protocols/Services, Virtualization, Shell Script, PHP.

## Responsabilities:

- Maintain network computer safe and healthy.
- Monitoring network services/devices.
- Technical Support
- Development of UTM solution

#### IT Infrastructure Analyst

Aug 2008 - Mar 2009

Lecom - http://www.lecom.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Router, Switches, Network Protocols/Services, Virtualization, Shell Script, PHP.

# Responsabilities:

- Maintain network computer safe and healthy.
- Monitoring network services/devices.
- Technical Support
- Development of UTM solution

## IT Infrastructure Analyst

Mar 2007 - Aug 2008

Inforeason - http://www.inforeason.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Router, Switches, Network Protocols/Services, Virtualization, Shell Script, PHP.

#### Responsabilities:

- Maintain network computer safe and healthy.
- Monitoring network services/devices.
- Technical Support
- Development of UTM solution

#### IT Intern

Mar 2004 - Aug 2005

Neobiz

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Shell Script, Network Protocols/Services.

## Responsabilities:

- Monitoring network services/devices.
- Technical Support

# Teaching Experience

## Teacher

Sep 2009 - Apr 2011

Senac - IT Technical College http://sp.senac.br/bauru

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Shell Script, Network Protocols/Services.

## Responsabilities:

- LPI Certification Course
- Cisco Certification Course
- Network Course

Mar 2009 - Dec 2009

Senac - IT Technical College http://sp.senac.br/jau

Main Technologies: Linux/Windows, Firewall, Shell Script,

Network Protocols/Services.

## Responsabilities:

- LPI Certification Course
- Cisco Certification Course
- Network Course

#### Skills Base

Programming Languages: C, Python;

Configuration Management Tools: SaltStack, ansible;

Orchestration/Provisioning Tools: Terraform, SaltStack;

Container Tools: Docker, Docker Swarm, Registry;

Virtualization: VirtualBox/vagrant, qemu/KVM, VMWare, libvirt, libguestfs, LXC;

Cloud: AWS, Digital Ocean, OpenStack;

## More Info

• Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/brunocriado

• Github: https://github.com/dropped

• Personal page: http://showmethe.codes